<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Useful Links on Reverse Engineering for Marist College</title>
    <link>/useful-links/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Useful Links on Reverse Engineering for Marist College</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 12:32:18 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/useful-links/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/useful-links/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 18:55:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/useful-links/resources/</guid>
      <description> Websites  RE subreddit Formal Program Analysis Reading Veteransec  Cybersecurity Community | Blog Posts and Other Writeups Buffer Overflow Tutorials  HackerNews  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Through Doing</title>
      <link>/useful-links/learn-through-doing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 12:36:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/useful-links/learn-through-doing/</guid>
      <description>Tools  IDA Freeware - Old version of commerical-grade dissassembler and debugger.  Learn More  Radare2 - Powerful dissassembler and debugger. CLI only, has some GUI extensions though. Online Compiler - Tool used in class to quickly demonstrate various compilations of C and C++ code. NSA Reversing Tool (GHIDRA) - Announcement of new government used tool for reversing.  More Info - Reddit thread discussing this announcement.  Free Online Dissassembler  Binary Exploitation Please be very careful as to where you are performing such exploits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Respected Professionals</title>
      <link>/useful-links/respected-professionals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 12:36:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/useful-links/respected-professionals/</guid>
      <description>Twitter  C-Level  Mark Rogers  Head of Security Operations at DEFCON VP Cybersecurity Strategy for Okta  Geoff Belknap  CSO of Slack  Michael Coates  Head of security at Mozilla Former CISO of Twitter   Journalism  Eric Geller  Cybersecurity reporter at @politico  Zack Whittaker  Security editor, @TechCrunch   Named  Amit Serper  Head of security research @cybereason Nocturnus  Matt Blaze  &amp;ldquo;Scientist, safecracker, professor, writer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>